football365.co.za 2012-12-26

# Football365.co.za - Privacy Policy

We at TEAMtalk media, (incorporating this site and all of the sites within our network - as seen on the footer of this website), strongly believe in protecting the confidentiality and security of information we collect about individuals. The material below describes our privacy policy and describes how we treat the information we receive about you if you interact with any of our sites.  

**Why We Need to Know About You**  

We need to know about you so that we can provide you with information on products and services and better target our sports content offering to your interests. What we need to know about you includes your address, age and preferences. 

**How We Learn About You**  

What we know about you we get mostly from you. But we may also have to find out more about you from other sources in order to make sure that what we know about you is correct and complete. We do not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such personally identifiable information may be gathered from competitions, message boards, suggestions and transactional areas. 

**Your Right To Opt Out**  

At our points of data collection, you have the opportunity to indicate whether you would like to "opt in" or "opt out" of receiving promotional and/or marketing information about other products, services and offerings from group companies and/or third parties on whose behalf we may send out information. Further, notwithstanding any opt out of promotional information by the user, we reserve the right to contact you regarding account status, changes to our service agreement and other matters relevant to the underlying service and/or the information collected. You can request to "opt out" of further promotional contacts at any time and all promotional emails we send you allow you this facility. Also, upon request, we will use commercially reasonable efforts functionally to delete you and your personal information from our database; however, it may be impossible to delete your entry without some residual information due to backups and records of deletions. 

**How We Protect What We Know About You**  

We treat what we know about you confidentially. Our employees take care in handling your information. They may get information about you only when there is a good reason to do so. We take steps to make our databases secure and to safeguard the information we have about you. 

**How We Use and Disclose What We Know About You**  

We may use anything we know about you to help us serve you better. We will not disclose your information to any third party save for the following exceptions: 

  * To help us process questions you may have about a purchase, registration or other inquiry you may have. 
  * To confirm or correct what we know about you. 
  * To help us or law enforcement agencies prevent fraud, money laundering, terrorism and other crimes. 
  * To allow for verification of what we know about you. 
  * Data processing requirements. 
  * Assisting an agency perform research for us. 
  * Compliance with the law or request of a government agency for example, complying with a search warrant. 
  * Compliance with an audit our business. 
  * If we sell all or any part of our business or merge with another company. 

Generally, we will disclose only the information we consider reasonably necessary to disclose. 

**How You Can See and Correct Your Information**  

Generally, we will let you review what we know about you if you ask us in writing or email. If you tell us that what we know about you is incorrect, we will review it. If we agree with you, we will correct our records. 

**Third Party Data Collection**  

You should be aware that sites within the group might sometimes permit third parties to offer you subscription, registration-based services, promotions or competitions through our network. We are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and users should check the applicable privacy policy of such party when providing personally identifiable information to other parties. 

**Sharing Your Data in Public Areas of our Sites**  

You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g. user name, e-mail address) on any of our message boards, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond our control. 

**How We Use IP Addresses**  

We may use your IP address to help diagnose any problems with our server or to administer our websites. Your IP address may be used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information that helps us understand user requirements. This specific information will only be used within our organisation and we will only share or use this information on an aggregate basis. 

**Links to Other Sites**  

Our site contains links to other sites outside of our control. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

**COOKIES**  

You should be aware that when you use our websites, mobile sites, or mobile apps, we may collect information by using 'cookies'.   

**What are cookies and how do they work?**  
Cookies are small bits of text that are downloaded to your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Your browser sends these cookies back to the website every time you visit the site again, so it can recognise you and can then tailor what you see on the screen.   

**What do you use cookies for?**  
Cookies are an important part of the internet. They make using websites much smoother and affect lots of the useful features of websites. There are many different uses for cookies, but they fall into four main groups.   

**Cookies that are neeed to provide the service you have asked for**  
Some cookies are essential so you can move around the website and use its features. Without these cookies, services you've asked for can't be provided. These cookies don't gather information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you've been on the internet.   

**Here are some examples of essential cookies.**  

Keeping you logged in during your visit; without cookies you might have to log in on every page you go to.  

When you add something to the online shopping basket, cookies make sure it's still there when you get to the checkout.  

Some are session cookies which make it possible to navigate through the website smoothly. However these are automatically deleted after you close your web browser.  

Improving your browsing experience  

These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make, such as your language or region and they provide improved features.   

Here are a few examples of just some of the ways that cookies are used to improve your experience on our websites.  

Remembering your preferences and settings, including marketing preferences.  

Remembering if you've filled in a survey, so you're not asked to do it again.  

Remembering if you've been to the site before. If you are a first-time user, you might see different content to a regular user.  

Restricting the number of times you're shown a particular advertisment. This is sometimes called 'frequency capping'.  

Showing you information that's relevant to products of ours that you have. 

Enabling social media components, like Facebook or Twitter. 

Showing 'related article' links that are relevant to the page you're looking at.  

Remembering a location you've entered such as weather forecasts.  

**Analytics**   
We like to keep track of what pages and links are popular and which ones don't get used so much to help us keep our sites relevant and up to date. It's also very useful to be able to identify trends of how people navigate (find their way through) our sites and if they get 'error messages' from web pages.   

This group of cookies, often called 'analytics cookies' are used to gather this information. These cookies don't collect information that identifies you. The information collected is anonymous and is grouped with the information from everyone else's cookies. We can then see the overall patterns of usage rather than any one person's activity. Analytics cookies only record activity on the site you are on and they are only used to improve how a website works.   

Some of our websites and some of the emails you might get from us also contain small invisible images known as 'web beacons' or 'tracking pixels'. These are used to count the number of times the page or email has been viewed and allows us to measure the effectiveness of its marketing and emails. These web beacons are anonymous and don't contain or collect any information that identifies you.   

We also use 'affiliate' cookies. Some of our web pages will contain promotional links to other companies' sites. If you follow one of these links and then register with or buy something from that other site, a cookie is sometimes used to tell that other site that you came from one of our sites. That other site may then pay us a small amount for the successful referral. This works using a cookie.   

**Showing advertising that is relevant to your interests**  

We sell space on some of our sites to advertisers. The resulting adverts often contain cookies. The advertiser uses the browsing information collected from these cookies to:   

1.restrict the number of times you see the same ad (frequency capping); and 

2.help show other ads that are relevant to you while you're on our websites. This is often called online behavioural advertising (OBA). OBA is a way of using information about your web-browsing activity, collected by using cookies, to group you with other users into interest groups and show you advertisements based on those interests. The OBA data collected from cookies you get when you're on our sites is only used to show relevant ads on our sites, not on other websites.  

Sometimes our websites contain ads for our own Sky products. These ads use cookies in the same way as described above.   

**So how does OBA work?**   
Let's look at an example. Imagine you visit a website about travel. That website shows an advert and with that advert you receive a cookie. Imagine you then visit one of our websites which has an advert from the same advertiser you saw on the travel site. The advertiser will give you a new version of the cookie you received on the travel site. The advertiser can then use that cookie to recognise that you've previously been to a travel site and show you a relevant ad.   

Although the OBA data collected uses your browsing activity to understand your interests, the data is anonymous and isn't linked to you as a person. Even if you log in to our websites, the OBA data is still not linked to you or your your Sky profile or subscription.   

Neither we, nor the companies who show ads on our sites sell data collected from cookies to any other organisations.   

Thank you for reading our privacy policy and thank you for choosing our network of sites as your reliable source of news and views on the Internet. If you have any questions about anything contained in this policy, you can contact our Customer Relations Team at: TEAMtalk media, 3rd Floor, The Warehouse, 24 Alfred Street, Cape Town, 8000, South Africa or e-mail us on customerrelations@teamtalkmedia.com. 

The foregoing policies are effective as of 1 May 2008. TEAMtalk media reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
